我们在零重力之中起舞
We can dance in zero G
飞速旅行到遥远的星际
Traveling fast far from galaxy
需要特殊的快递吗
Need a special delivery
只需叫上Malo Korrigan
Just call Malo Korrigan
但不是免费的
But it's not free
Malo Korrigan
没人能打倒你
Nobody will bring you down
Malo Korrigan
生活在宇宙中
live in space
翻译、时间轴、后期：Bolshevik0
#2              老兵
Jonas, don't let those thrusters give out.
Jonas 别让那些推进器坏掉
Speck of dust blowing in a windstorm.
就像是风暴里的一片沙
Judge one way of putting it.
我正在想着怎么把它放进去
They feel more like an ice cream cone
感觉就像冰激凌筒的圆锥
stuck in the middle of a go volcano.
卡在火山口似的
注:
飞船上的零部件按里程说使用寿命应该也行
This black tritanium fuel cell was supposed to
这个黑色的钛合金燃料电池
last another three trillion light-years.
像是快用了一万亿光年了
Isn't it covered by a warranty?
难道没有保修吗
Kid, you gotta be kidding.
孩子 你开玩笑吧
I bought it from your godless brothers
我从你那些不信神的兄弟那儿买来的
and I'll give them a piece on my mind.
甚至没付钱
Hang on old-timer cuz we're in for a rough landing.
老伙计抓稳了 因为我们要硬着陆了
Jonas, fire retrorockets 1, 2 and 3 at full power.
Jonas 让1 2 3号反推引擎满推力点火
You were great baby.
你很棒啊
Sorry it was so hard but you really came through.
尽管状况很糟糕但你还是撑过来了
Shouldn't you be wearing a spacesuit, princess?
公主你不该穿着太空服吗
The atmosphere on this planet isn't very comfortable.
这个星球的大气不是很好
Not for you.
对你而言不是很好
But I like breathing carbon monoxide at sub-zero temperatures.
不过我还是挺喜欢呼吸这温度在零下的一氧化碳气体
So what's the problem?
所以有什么问题
Well I'll tell you what the problem is?
我来告诉你是什么问题
Trying to find a tritanium fuel cell in this planetary junkyard.
在这片行星级的垃圾场上找一个钛合金燃料电池
It's not a junkyard.
这可不是垃圾场
It's more like a museum.
这更像是一个博物馆
Every single vessel and weapon that was used in the Sewalik Wars
各种各样在Sewalik Wars中使用过的载具和武器
is now gather and rust on this planet.
现在都聚集在这座星球上腐烂着
Galloping galaxies.
天哪
The thermal shield was damaged when we landed.
热防护盾在我们着陆时被烧坏了
And I want to do extra repairs.
所以我现在需要进行些额外的维修
I wanna be your lover.
我想成为你的恋人
Maybe you'd do but I wanna be mad about you.
也许你不想这样但我还是迷恋着你
You're still crying baby.
可你还在哭着
Want us to wait for you?
需要我们等你吗
No thanks.
不用了 谢谢
Go look for a tritanium fuel cell.
去找那个钛合金燃料电池吧
Mark 87, man,
要Mk.87型号的
when I'm finished here I'll go prospective around.
我修完的时候会四处找找的
Ten to one we will find it before you do.
我有九成把握比你先找到
Oh yeah.
哦
Cyana, you got a bet.
Cyana 你打赌吗
Say you two.
你俩
Maybe you should take all best you want. Just in case.
应该带上最好的东西 以防万一
Not a chance.
不用了
Your proton gun is more dangerous
你的质子枪
than an overheated nuclear reactor.
甚至比过热的核反应堆还危险
So long.
再见
Look at all the starfighters,
看看这些太空战船
neutron missiles and bomber drones.
中子导弹和无人轰炸机
This place is crazy.
这个地方很疯狂
Wars are always crazy.
战争总是很疯狂
And the Sewalik Wars were crazier than the most.
而Sewalik Wars是最疯狂的战争
On the other hand, the 12 mother planets grew so weary of fighting
另外一方面 12个母星厌倦了战争
but they decided to unite
于是他们决定联合起来
and that's how the Cosmocratic League was born.
这就是星际联盟诞生的原因
Let me try.
让我试试
I love being humiliated.
我喜欢被当众羞辱
Looks like I've won the bet.
看起来我赢得了赌局
Hey, Jonas. Is the mark 75 compatible?
嘿 Jonas Mk.75型号兼容吗
You may think I'm saying this
你觉得我会因为赌局
because of the bet but no.
而说这个型号不行
We need at least two mark 87.
但实际上我们至少需要两个Mk.87型号
You sure?
你确定吗
At the academy I learned that it's all go...
以前在学校学习的时候我了解到这都是兼容的
Forget what you learn to the academy.
忘记你以前在学校学过的那些东西
Those starchy old professors never set foot in an engine room.
那些迂腐的教授从来没进过引擎舱
Besides, I've got...
而且 我有...
Jonas?
Jonas
Jonas, come in.
Jonas 回答我
Jonas!
Jonas
He's not responding.
他没回音
What's going on?
咋回事
Let's go!
我们走
Cyana! Be careful!
Cyana 小心点
You don't know what you're gonna find down there.
你不知道往下走会走到哪儿
Jonas?
Jonas
Jonas where are you?
Jonas你在哪儿
Jonas!
Jonas
Well, what did you find?
你发现了什么
Our entire cargo of holographic screens has vanished
我们整货舱的全息屏幕都不见了
and so has Jonas.
Jonas也不见了
Malo, there may be a way to locate Jonas.
Malo 也许有个方法能定位到Jonas
I'm listening.
我听着呢
If his communicator still functioning,
如果他的通讯器还在工作
we should be able to home in on his frequency.
在他的频率上 我们能对准并靠近他
All right it's working.
好的 这起作用了
His signal is straight ahead of us.
他的信号在我们的前方
Range 5,000 meters.
距离5千米
and it's moving.
现在在移动
Hang in there old tracer.
坚持住啊 老牛仔
We're on our way.
我们在路上了
Range 2,000 meters. We're getting closer.
距离2千米 我们正在接近
Signals very close now.
现在信号离我们非常近了
So why haven't we found him?
但为什么我们还没找到他
Jonas!
Jonas
This is a joke cuz it isn't funny.
这是个不好笑的玩笑
Oh no!
哦不
The signal isn't coming from here.
信号并不是从这发出来的
He may be alright.
他也许还好
Without his helmet?
在没有头盔的情况下吗
I can survive in a frigid carbon monoxide atmosphere
我能在寒冷的一氧化碳大气中生存
but Jonas can't.
但Jonas不行
Jonas.
Jonas
Cyana, the signal's moving again.
Cyana 信号再次移动了
The old codger's still alive
老伙计还活着
and he's somewhere over there.
他可能就在那边
Get out of there.
快离开那儿
Watch out.
小心
Ah!
啊
Cyana!
Cyana
Where are we?
我们在哪儿
Inside an XP class transport rig,
在XP级别的运输船里
one of the biggest vessels used during the Sewalik Wars.
在Sewalik Wars中使用的最大的飞船之一
I'm still getting a signal.
我还能收到信号
Jonas seems to be nearby.
Jonas还在附近
Let's go check it out.
我们去找找看
The thing that attacked us, do you have any idea what it is?
你知道那个攻击我们的东西是什么吗
Probably a battle robot left over from the wars.
也许是大战中遗留下来的战斗机器人
But I thought all the weapons were deactivated
但我以为所有武器都被关闭了
before being dumped here.
在遗弃在这里之前
Seems like someone decided to break the rules.
看起来有些人打算违反规定
If that's true then we have to notify the authorities about this.
如果这是真的 那我们应该告知有关方面
Malo, look!
Malo 瞧
There's our missing cargo, the holographic screens.
这就是我们丢失的货物 全息屏幕
But how did they end up in here?
但为什么它们被放在这里
I got a clue.
我知道了
Stay still.
不要动
Go!
走
Combat unit FAR422 mission.
战斗单位FAR422的任务是
Defend frontlines and repel enemy attack against oppositions.
防御前线战场并击退任何对友军的攻击
BA2568A125 sustained enemy attack.
BA2568A125遭受到了敌人的攻击
Intruders neutralized.
入侵者已被消灭
Attempting to contact headquarters
尝试联系指挥部
and submit urgent request for reinforcements.
并请求立即援助
Amazing!
真厉害
He thinks he's still fighting in the Sewalik Wars.
他仍认为自己在Sewalik Wars中战斗
I guess some fool of a general didn't disconnect him properly.
我认为有些愚蠢的将军没有把他正确地关闭
Jonas is still close by.
Jonas还在附近
Follow me.
跟我来
What are they?
这都是些什么
Shh! Quiet.
嘘 安静
More battle robots, a whole squadron of them.
更多的战斗机器人 将近一个中队的数量
Combat unit FAR422 attempt to contact headquarters has failed.
战斗单位FAR422无法联系到指挥部
Combat unit FAR422 mission's defend frontlines
战斗单位FAR422的任务是防御前线战场
Executing the technical operations
执行技术性操作
to obtain a necessary reinforcements.
以获得必要的援兵
That metal monstrosity is reactivating
这个金属的怪兽正在通过我们的货物
the other robots using our cargo.
重启其他机器人
There is reinforcements.
这些就是援兵
He's building himself an army.
他在为自己建造一个军队
Hey!
嘿
What?
怎么了
He has the same move with Jonas.
他的操作方式和Jonas一样
Jonas's signal is right under us.
Jonas的信号就在我们下面
But that's where the robot is.
但那就是机器人的位置
Jonas is in the robot.
Jonas在机器人里
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办
We're gonna get him out.
我们把他救出来
Come on!
快来
Combat unit FAR422 under attack by enemy forces.
战斗单位FAR422被敌军攻击
Mission defend oppositions and eliminate intruders immediately.
任务是保护友军并立刻消灭入侵者
You sure this is a good idea?
你确定这是个好主意吗
No, it's the only one I got.
不是 但这是我唯一能想到的
Eliminating intruders! Eliminating intruders!
消灭入侵者 消灭入侵者
Eliminating intruders! Eliminating intruders! Eliminating intruders!
消灭入侵者 消灭入侵者 消灭入侵者
Follow me!
跟着我
Jonas, can you hear me?
Jonas 你能听见我吗
Combat unit FAR422......
战斗单位FAR422...
Jonas!
Jonas
This is bad now.
情况很糟糕
The robot is downloading Jonas's mind
机器人正在把Jonas脑中的数据
into it's own operating systems.
下载到他自己的系统里
Hang in there, old buddy.
老伙计 坚持住
%$^%@#
Well, well.
诶 诶
What?
怎么了
The central processor was made by the Consortium.
中央处理器是由财团制造的
But the Consortium didn't exist during the Sewalik Wars.
但是Sewalik Wars期间财团还不存在
I suspect that our friend Yago rigged this robot
我怀疑我们的朋友Yago控制了这个机器人
to build a secret army for the Consortium.
来为财团制造一个秘密军队
But he failed.
但是他失败了
Eliminating intruders! Eliminating intruders! Eliminating intruders!
消灭入侵者 消灭入侵者 消灭入侵者
Jonas!
Jonas
Speak to me.
能说话吗
Looks like I win that bet after all, you two.
看起来我最后还是赢得了赌局
What?
什么
Look up there.
看看那儿
tritanium fuel cell.
钛合金燃料电池
It's a mark 87.
是Mk.87型号的
Yeah I found it.
没错我找到了
Jonas you're a crafty old kittens.
Jonas你真是狡猾
There's a dozens of mark 87s in here,
这还有很多Mk.87型号的电池
which will be able to sell to your godless brothers.
也许以后能卖给你那不信神的老兄
We're gonna end up making a tidy profit on this run.
这回我们收获颇丰
But first I want to do some repair work on our robot.
但首先我想修理一下我们的机器人
Are you kidding?
你开玩笑吧
The FAR422 has been deactivated for good.
FAR422这回算是彻底销毁了
That's what you think.
你是这么认为的
But I'm an even crafty-year-old cooler than you realize.
但我比你以为的还要狡猾
Since the robot had the good taste to trying download my knowledge,
因为这个机器人的品位不错 尝试着下载我的知识
I figured I'd teach him a few tricks.
我认为应该教他点技巧
Wipe out any trace of the Sewalik Wars or the Consortium.
并抹掉所有关于Sewalik Wars或者财团的记忆
quiberon quasars
Does I ever go down?
我有失败过吗
Good.
很好
What I was stuck on the inside of that oversized tin soldier,
当我困在那个巨大的金属机器人里的时候
I was convinced that I never eat... come again.
我以为我再也不能逃出来了
By the way, Jonas, exactly what kind of tricks did you teach that robot?
Jonas 顺便问一下 你教了那个机器人什么技巧
No! Nothing very complicated. Just a few basic peaceful procedures.
没啥特别复杂的 就是一些基本的和平的程序
But I did give the robot my greatest talent.
但是我确实把我最好的才能给了他
Don't laugh, Kiwk Kiwk.
Kiwk Kiwk 别笑
He doesn't mean his talent is a cook.
这不意味着他最好的才能是做饭
But as a mechanic.
但应该是维修方面的
Am I right, Jonas?
我说得对吗 Jonas
You stand right in baby
But I'll come back to you
She gave me a basic five will be alright
Baby, whoop!
我们在零重力之中起舞
We can dance in zero G
飞速旅行到遥远的星际
Traveling fast far from galaxy
Malo Korrigan
没人能打倒你
Nobody will bring you down
Malo Korrigan
生活在宇宙中
live in space